Gael Greene Magazine Collection 1968-2008 MSS.392
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Magazines
  - May 12, 1980 - December 20, 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 6)
    -8/3/81. NYM, 14, No.30, (Odeon, Joanna, Nuccio). "Eat And Be Seen." P.43-46
    -10/12/81. NYM, Vol.14, No.40 (Rangoon Burmese Kitchen). "Road to Rangoon." P.89
    -10/26/81. NYM, Vol.14, No.42 (Holiday Entertaining: Beatiful Meals). "Dinner by Design," Lofty Ideas." P.48-53
    -11/30/81. NYM, Vol.14, No.47 (Meadowlands). "Racetrack Dining All Day Long, Doo-Dah, Doo-Dah." P.56-57
    -2/1/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.5 (Chatfield's, The Seafood Room at David K's, John, Clancy's, Devon House, Elmer's, Sparks, Franky and Johnny's, Cincinnati, Trader Vic's). "The Good, the Bad and the So-So."P.32-35
    -3/8/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.10 (Le Perigord). "Nouvelle Bounce at Le Perigord." P.48-49
    -4/12/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.15 (Helmsley Palace, Waldorf-Astoria, Grand Hyatt, Regency, Carlyle, Mayfair Regent, Parker Meridien, Hotel Inter-Continental, Berkshire Place, Plaza, Park Lane, La Cote Basque, Fraunces Travern, Sylvia's, Cupping Room Cafe, Market Diner, Kiev, Famous Dairy Restaurant, Cornelia Street Cafe, Brasserie, McDonalds, White Wave, Richoux of London, Eclair Bakery and Restaurant, Hao Shih Chieh, Hee Seung Fung). "Breakfasts of Champions."P.42-54
    -5/3/82.NYM, Vol.15, No.18 (Vanessa's, Shun Lee West, One Fifth, Frank's, Texarkana, Four Seasons, Szechuan House, La Camelia, Ristorante Primavera, Cafe Un Deux Trois, Fiorella, Chin-Ya, Capsuto Freres, J.S.Vandam, Greenery Cafe, La Coupole, La Gamelle, Evelyn's Kitchen, Cafe 58, Carnegie Deli, El Gaucho, Elaine's, Elmer's, Home Village Restaurant, Il Monello, Joanna, La Gauloise, Marylou's, Maxwell's Plum, Nanni al Valletto, Nicola's, Odeon, Russian Tea Room, 21, Uzie's). "Late-Late New York: Where Should We Eat."P.32-51
    -10/25/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.42 (Hoilday Entertaining). "Great Parties Around the Clock."P.39-48
    -11/22/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.46 (Meals on Wheels). "Food for Thought."P.24-25
    -12/20/82. NYM, Vol.15, No.50, (DDL Foodshow). "Dino's Foodshow." P.68-70
  - December 27, 1982 - November 7, 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
    -2/7/83. NYM Vol.16, No.6, (Le Perigord Park, La Cote Basque, Maurice, Le Recolte, Le Perigord, Claude's, La Folie, Le Cygne, La Grenouille, REgine's, Le Lavandou, Le Chantilly, Cafe Argenteuil, Le Madrigal). "Gael Greene Ranks the Great French Restaurants of New York."P.28-41
    -2/14/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.7 (Le Plasir). "Plaisir By Any Other Name."P.75
    -2/21/83. NYM, Vol. 16, No.8 (The Polo Restaurant). "Shooting for the Stars at the Polo." (2) P.60-61
    -2/28/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.9 (The Water Club). "Barge It." P.72-74
    -4/11/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.15 (Castellano). "Venetian Vanities."P.66-68
    -4/18/1983. NYM. 15th Anniversary Issue.
    -5/16/83.NYM, Vol. 16, No.20 (Teuscher Chocolates', Michel Guerard, Manon, La Violette, Peyrano, Godiva, Li-lac Chocolates, Inc, Paron, Chocolates by "M", Brommer, Neuchatels, Papillon's, Lindt, Lenotre, Maison du Chocolat, Perugina, Kron, Neuhaus, Corne Toison d'Or, Davies Candies, Stork's Pastry Shop, Mondel Chocolates, Ellens, Elk Candy Company, Bartons', Balducci's, Bloomingdale's, DDL Foodshow). "The Chocolate Elite." P.40-53
    -5/30/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.22, (Orso). "Don't Ask For the Moon --- Orso Has the Stars." 66-67
    -6/20/83. NYM, Vol.17, No.25 (Vecchia Roma, Ambasciata d'Abruzzo, Checchino dal 1887, Papa Giovanni, Ristorante GB Trattoria Toscano al Girarrosto, Pizzeria Moroni, Antica Porchetta, Giolitti, Gelateria Della Palma, Sant'Eustachio, Tre Scalini, Coco Lezzone, Tredicigobbi, Rivoire, San Domenico, Gambrinus, Scaletta, Savini, Gualtiero Marchesi, Peek). "Italy: The Real Stuff."P.36-47
    -7/18/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.28, (Auntie Yuan). "A Theatre of Taste." P.65-66
    -7/25/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.29 (Erminia). "I'll Take Romance." P.59-61
    -9/12/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.36 (Godiva, New York Ice, Ben and Jerry's Homemade, Alpen Zauber, Angelica, Gelato Modo, Sant Ambroeus, Steve's Ice Cream, David,'s Ice Cream, Flavor Factory). "The Ice-Cream Renaissance." (2) P.62-77
    -10/3/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.39, (Cafe Luxembourg). "A Breakthrough on the Western Front." P.72-73
    -11/7/83. NYM, Vol.16, No.44 (Michel Rostang, Le Bernardin, L'Archestrate, La Mere Blanc, Restaurant Girardet, Chantecler, L'Amandier de Mougins, Relais a Mougins,) "Gael Greene with the Latest From France."P.34-45
  - December 26, 1983 - December 31, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
    -12/26/83-1/4/84. NYM, Vol.17, No.1 (Cafe L:uxembourg, Orso, Ernie's Le Zine, Peonie's, Xenia, New Deal, Pari Passu, Mister Chow) "Cruising." P.88-92
    -2/13/84. NYM, Vol17, No.7 (Fine & Schapiro's, Carnegie, 2nd Ave. Deli, Pastrami Factory, Stage Delicatessen, Kaplan's at the Delmonico, Wolf's). "Pot Luck."P.42-44
    -2/27/84. NYM, Vol17, No.9 (Aunti Yuan, Cafe Luxembourg, Chanterelle, Elaine's, Four Seasons, Greene Street, Jasmin's Era, La Recolte, La Tablita, Le Cirque, Maurice, Nathan's, Famous, Odeon, Oyster Bar, Quilted Giraffe, River Cafe, Russian Tea Room, Sparks Steak House, Shun Lee West, Slyvia's Restaurant, Tavern on the Green, Terrace Restaurant, Windows on the World, Wylie's Ribs & Co). Ask Gael: "Personal favorites."P.49-52
    -3/5/84. NYM, Vol.17, No.10, (Regent Air). "Gilt Trip."P.72-73
    -3/26/84. NYM, Vol.17, No.13 (Roxanne's). "Applause, Applause."P.74-76
    -4/16/84. NYM, Vol.17, No.16 (Hard Rock Cafe, Jezebel). "Southern Nights." P.94-98
    -7/2-7/9/84. NYM, (Gianni's, Roebling's, North Star Pub, Sweets, Coho, Futlon Street Cafe, Sloppy Louie's, David's Cookies, PIzza del Ponte, South Street Sausage Comapnay, Ming's Bau, Jimbay, Fulton Market Raw Bar, Acropolis, Beekman Street Bakery, Burger Boys of Brooklyn, Ice Cream Extravaganza, Sweet Stuff, New York Egg Cream, Gaylord's Saffron, New York Fries, Everything Yogurt, New York Pastrami Factory, Bon Pain, D.J. Garrett & Company, Pasta & Cheese 1-2-3, Larmen Dosanko, Great Manhattan Chicken & Rib Company, Empanadas). "South Street: Sampling the Seaport."P.42-68
    -7/30/84. NYM (Sea Grill, American Festival Cafe, Savories). "Rockefeller Center Renaissance."P.34-39
    -9/24/84. NYM, (Jams, La Colonna, Jean Lafitte, The Manhattan Ocean Club, Manhattan Cafe, Roxanne's, Gotham Bar & Grill). "What's Hot What's Not." (2)P.80-88
    -10/8/84. NYM (Mezzaluna). "Half-Moon Over Manhattan." P72-74
    -10/22/84.NYM (Hotel Plaza Athenee). "There's a Small Hotel."P.128-132
    -10/29/84. NYM, (Cafe 43). "Blessing on Broadway."P.70-71
    -11/12/84. NYM (El Internacional). "The Tapa-Dance Kid." P.115-116
    -11/19/84. NYM (World Yacht Enterprises). "A Floatable Feast."P.67-68
    -11/19/84. NYM (Stuffed Prunes, Dean, & DeLuca). "The Phases of Prune." P.51
    -12/3/84. NYM (Jerry's Bar & Mesquite Grill). "Mesquite on the Hudson."P.145-146
    -12/24-31/84. NYM (photos). The Ultimate New York. P. 69-70
  - January 28, 1985 - December 30, 1985 (Box 9)
    -1/28/85. NYM (Parioli Romanissimo, Felidia, Bravo Gianni, Barbetta, Primavera, La Camelia, Il Nido, Girafe, Nanni al Valletto, L'Hostaria del Bongustaio, Giambelli 50th, Romeo Salta, Italian Pavilion, Prima Donna, Positano, Elaines's, Mezzaluna, Ecco, Elio's, Il Cantinori, Gino, Orso, La Colonna, Uzies, Castellano, Georgine Carmella, Sistina, Gordon's, De Marco, Scarlatti, Paola's, La Sirena, Lattanzi, Dal Barone). "That's Italian." (2) P.36-57
    -2/25/85. NYM (Memphis). "I Know Why the Cajun Sings." (2) P.64-65
    -3/18/85. NYM (Arcadia). "Falling in Like."P.82-83
    -4/8/85. NYM (Il Mulino, Cent'Anni, Erminia, Contrapunto, Zinno, Trastevere, Rao's, Trattoria da Alfredo, Il Monello, Salta in Boca, Tre Scalini, Divino, Da Silvano, Nicola Paone, Lusardi's, Campagnola, Cavaliere, Nanni, Ennio & Michael, Parma, Lello, Pinocchio, Joe's Restaurant, Patsy's, Alfredo). "That's Italian, Part II." P.45-67
    -4/29/85. NYM (Sandro's). "The Real Thing."P.85-86
    -6/8/85. NYM (James Beard). "The Father of Us All."P.68-69
    -6/17/85. (America, Positano, Canastel's, Montrachet, Azzurro, Safari Grill, Memphis, Cajun, Gulf Coast) What's Going On...Food: "Where's Today's Hot Grazing Spot."
    -6/24/85. NYM (Gotham Bar & Grill, Montrachet). "American Dreams."P.70-71
    -7/1-8/85. NYM (Fiorello, Fiorella, John's, Hoexter's Cafe, Soho Kitchen and Bar, Orso, Patsy's, Pizza Joint, David's Cookies, Prima Donna, Ray's Pizza, Totonno, Arturo's, Fifth Avenue Grill, Petaluna, Paradise Pizza Cafe, Ernie's, Tom's Pizzeria, Famous Ray's Pizza in the Village, Mezzaluna, Zipz's Pizza, John's, V & T, La Focacceria, Canastel's, America, Ancora, Original Ray's, Pizzapiazza, Cafe Mortimer, Rugantino's Pizza, Aiello's Pizza Emporium, Peppino's Pizza, Century Cafe, American Pie, Pizzeria Uno, Vinnie's, Mama's Famous Pan Pizza, Pizza Box, Rocky Lee Chu-cho Bianco, Goldberg's Pizzeria, Godfather's Pizza, Bella Pizza, Ray Bari, Bar Lui, Trattoria Pino, Ray Bari's, Ray's of Greenwich Village). "The Joy of Pizza."P.40-50
    -9/30/85. NYM (Fifth Avenue Grill, Soho Kitchen and Bar, Petaluma, America, Bar Lui). "Gael Grazes." P50-59
    -11/25/85. NYM (Arizona 206, Pizzico). "Westward, Haute!"P.100-104
    -12/23-30/85. NYM (Windows on the World, Le Cirque, Zabar's, EAT, Policastro, D&G, Papaya King, Carnegie Deli, Utica Joe's, Hoexter's, SoHo Kitchen, John's PIzza, Fiorello, Maxwell's Plum, Caramba!, El Parador, Gotham Bar & Grill, Santa Fe, Cafe Marimba, Rosa Mexicana, John Clancy, Dallas BBQ, Fischer Brothers & Leslie, Petak, Chirping Chicken, Fine & Schapiro, Regency Hotel, Keh's Auntie Yuan, Shun Lee Palace, Petrossian, Jams, Chanterelle, Quilted Giraffe, An American Place, Palm, Peter Luger, Lutece, Maurice, Le Perigord, La Cote Basque, The Odeon, Cafe Luxembourg, Cafe des Artistes, Restaurant Florent, River Cafe) The Best of New York.P. 71-109
  - January 6, 1986 - June 1, 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
    -1/6/86, NYM, Vol.19, Issue 1. (Aurora). "Joe Baum Goes for the 'Whoosh'." P.59 (TX-4-826-616) through 12-1-86
    -1/20/86, NYM, Vol.19, issue 2 (Harry's Bar). "Twice in Love With Harry's." P.49
    -2/17/86, NYM, Vol.19, issue 7 (Buona Tavola). "A FIne Madness." (2) P.122-123
    -2/24/86, NYM, Vol 19, issue 8 (Le Bernardin) "Le Bernardin Beguiles our Crocodile." P.72
    -3/17/86, NYM Vol 19, issue 11 (Hasaki). "My Pet Jackfish." P.81
    -4/14/86, NYM, Vol 19, issue 15 (Palio). "Galloping Consumption." P.96
    -5/26/86.NYM, Vol 19, issue 21 (Caffe Roma). "Torrid Zone." P.72
    -6/16/86, NYM, Vol.19, issue 24 (Canyon Ranch) "Gael Takes it Off: Calorie Counting at Canyon Ranch." P.48-50
    -7/14/86., NYM, Vol 19, issue 27 (Chez Louis, Hulot's, La Boheme, Chapiteau, Sel & Poivre, Tapis Rouge). "Beaucoup de Bistros." P.44
    -12/1/86. (Shun Lee Cafe, Sign of the Dove, Blake's Grill, Silverbird, Fandango, Lafayette). "Cruising." P. 104
    -12/22-29/86, NYM, Vol.19, issue, "The Power that will be:Food: Gilbert Le Coze" .76
    -1/5/87, NYM, Vol, 20, issue 1 Ask Gael (Gotham Bar and Grill, Le Bernardin, Arizona 206, Le Cirque, Sandro, Felidia, Primavera, Barbetta's, Il Mulino, Barocco, La Tulipe, HSF, Silver Palace, Maxwell's Plum, Tavern on the Greene, Pig Heaven, Serendipity 3, Soho Kitchen and Bar, American Festival Cafe, Chez Louis, Sparks, Palm, Hard Rock Cafe, Grotta Azzurra, Auntie Yuan, Edwardian Room, Cafe des Artistes, Adam Rib, Takesushi, Mitsukoshi, Hasaki, Sushizen, Ballroom, Lutece, Sylvia, John Clancy, Janice's, Fish Place, Oyster Bar, Bravo Gianni, Contrapunto, Georgine Carmella, Trastevere, Trastevere 84, Jams, Cote Basque, Windows on the world, America, Palio, Elaine's, Peter Luger, 4Seasons, Batons, Ciaobella, Le Perigord, Maurice, Georgine Carmella, Il Cortile, Fiorello's, Fiorella's, John's, La Boheme, Freddy and Pepe's, Famous Sammy's Roumanian Steakhouse, Maurice, Marie-Michelle, Nathan's Famous, Carnegie Deli, Carolina, Nells, Quatorze, TJ Tucker, Indochine, Mezzaluna, Jim McMullen, Mary Lou's, Sam's, Canastel's, Acme, Cafe Sphinx, Ecco, Key Cafe, Madam Rosa's, Mortimer's, River Cafe, Brive, Ermina, Wylie's, Bobby Rubino's, Fine and Schapiro, Second Ave Kosher Deli, Texarkana, Petrossian, Cafe Marimba, Benito I, Rao's, Provence, Tablita, Shun Lee, CAfe Luxembourg, Bud's, Odeon, Montrachet, Greene Street. Chanterelle (cover story). (TX-4-713-811) through 12-28-87 (2 copies)
    -1/12/87, NYM, Vol.20, issue 2 (Cityside: Citymeals). "Old Friends." P.10
    -1/26/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 4 (Provence, Barocco). "A Couple of Swells." P.60
    -3/9/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 10 (Safari Grill, Border Café, Cinco de Mayo, Buds) "Four for the Money." P.102-105
    -3/23/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 12 (Le Cirque, Le Regence, Le Chantilly, Le Festival). "The French Evolution." P.50-55 (2 copies)
    -4/27/87, NYM Vol 20, issue 17 (Albero d'Oro, The Cafe at Arizona 206). "Branching Out." P.130-132
    -5/11/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 19, (Restaurant Sofi). "Sofi's Choice." p. 80
    -6/1/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 22 ('21') "Adding Up the New '21'." P.40-47
  - June 8, 1987 - April 18, 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
    -6/8/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 23 (Coastal)"Coastal Discoveries." P.70-71
    -6/22/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 25 (Anatolia). "Turkey on a Roll." P.76-77
    -7/27/87, NYM, Vol.20, issue 29, Aspen. (Gordon's, Grill on the Park, Lauretta's, Takah, Little Annie's, Primavera, Abetone, Steak Pit, Smuggler Land Office Ltd, Cooper Street Pier, Bentley's, La Cocina, Cantina, Mama Maria's, Pizza-on-Wheels, Shlomo's, Poppycocks, Brand Building, Hotel Lenado, Hotel Jerome, St. Moritz Lodge). "True West." 44-50
    -8/10/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 31 (Le Palmier, Bellini by Cipriani, American Festival Cafe). "Such Good Fronds."P.52-53
    -9/14/87, NYM, Vol, 20 issue 36 (Extra! Extra! Extra!, Cameos, Vico, Manhattan Island). "In the Nabes." P.63-65
    -10/5/87, NYM, Vol 20 issue 39 (Bouley) "Vaulting Ambition." P75-76
    -10/19/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 41 (St Peterbourg, Odessa, Kavkasian). "Borscht Belt." P.116-118
    -11/16/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 45 (Melrose, China Grill). "California Dreaming." P.102-104
    -11/30/87, NYM, Vol 20, issue 47 (David K's, Zarela). "Home on Two Ranges." P.90-95
    -12/21-12/87NYM, Vol 20, issue 50 (Le Pavillon). Remember This Le Pavillon. P. 86
    -1/4/88. v. 21 # (Brive, Aquavit, Extra! Extra!, Arizona 206, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, Chez Louis, Gotham Bar & Grill, Oyster Bar, Manhattan Ocean Club, John Clancy's, Melrose, La Tulipe, ome on the Range, North Garden Restaurant, H.S.F., Bo Ky, Mezzogiorno, Le Chantilly, Sammy's Roumanian Steak House, Cafe des Artistes, Tavern on the Green, Petrossian, Ideal's, Le Cirque, Sofi, Arcadia, La Cote Basque, Montrachet, Four Seaons, Post House, Afghan Kebab House, Jamaican Hot Pot Restaurant, Annabelle, Remi, Giancarlo, Arizona Cafe, Cafe Society, Canal Bar, Cave Canem, China Grill, Orsini's, Shun Lee Cafe, Coastal, Cameos, Baci, Sparks, Sammy's, Dawat, Barocco, Provence, Montrachet, Rakel, Rainbow Room). "Ask Gael: Where to Go in '88." Vol. 21 Iss# 1 pp. 17-19
    -2/8/88. (Rainbow Room). "Over the Rainbow Room." Vol. 21 Iss# 6 pp. 38-46
    -3/21/88. (Trixie's, Tamara). "Two on the Aisle." Vol. 21 Iss# 11 pp.86-87
    -3/28/88. (Eze, Mondial). "Rooms of Their Own." Vol. 21 Iss# 12 pp.105-109
    -4/11/88 NYM, Vol21, issue 15,"Best Bet,"What's your Fantasy, A chocolate Phone you can nibble, while on hold" (Chocolate Indulgences)
    -4/18/88. (La Cote Basque, Zabar). "Restaurants: Fast Food, The Poor: Soup Kitchen, Food: Valhalla" Vol. 21 Iss# 15 pp.72-74
  - May 9, 1988 - April 17, 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    -5/9/88. France (Maison Blanche, L'Ambroisie, Les Gourmets des Ternes, L'Ami Louis, Stresa, Chez Toutone, Le Bistrot d'a Cote, Jamin, Guy Savoy, Le Louis XV, Le Royal Gray, Hotel Gray d'Albion, Cote d' Or, Jean-Pierre Billoux, A la Cote Saint-Jacques). "Plain & Francey." (2) Vol. 21 Iss# 18 pp. 46-59
    -5/30/88. (Metro). "Tracking Metro."Vol. 21 Iss# 21 pp. 72-77
    -7/18/88. (Maxwell's Plum, Jerry's). "Trio con Brio." Vol. 21 Iss#27 pp. 41-43
    -8/15/88. (Four Seasons, Victory Cafe, Savant, Texarkana, Shun Lee Palace, Bravo Gianni, Rakel, Lafayette, Gotham Bar & Grill, Shun Lee Palace, David K's Cafe, Le Bernardin, Evergreen Room, Lutece, Palio, Brive, Zarela, Le Cirque). "How to Eat Healthy at New York's Great Restaurants." Vol. 21 Iss#32 pp. 28-36
    -8/29/88. (Rancho La Puerta). "Losing It Again." Vol. 21 Iss#34 pp. 43-46
    -9/26/88. (Mondrian). "A Jewel From Jersey." Vol. 21 Iss# 38 pp. 122-123
    -10/3/88. (San Domenico, Sfuzzi)."Ciao-Chow." Vol. 21 Iss#39 pp. 62-63
    -10/17/88. (Huberts, Le Laurier). "Brain Food." Vol. 21 Iss#40 pp. 72-74
    -10/31/88. (Star Fish Grill, Luma). "Catch A Rising Star Fish."Vol. 21 Iss#43 pp.99-100
    -11/14/88. (Carnegie Deli, Golden's Restaurant & Deli, Stage Deli, Second Avenue Deli). "Tempest in a Glass Tea." Vol. 21 Iss#45 pp. 63-72
    -11/21/88. (Andiamo, Poiret). "West Side Glory." Vol. 21 Iss#46 130-131
    -12/12/88. (Aureole). "Charles In Charge."Vol. 21 Iss#49 pp. 93-94
    -12/19-26/88. (Rainbow Room). "The Most Romantic Restaurant: Lost in the Stars." Vol. 21 Iss#50 pp. 102
    -1/2/89. v. 22 # (Adam's Rib, Ambassador Grill, Andiamo, Arizona 206 Cafe, Auntie Yuan, Aurora, Baci, Ballroom, Bernard's, Bostro du Nord, Brive, Cafe Luxembourg, Caffe Dante, Cameos, Canal Bar, Chanterelle, Chez Louis, China Grill, Coastal, da Umberto, David K's Cafe, Dawat, Dean & DeLuca, Eze, Fiorello's, Four Seasons, Golden Unicorn, Gotham Bar & Grill, Greene Street Cafe, Grotta Azzurra, Jamaican Hot Pot, John's Pizza, Jonathan Waxman, La Boheme, La Caravelle, L a Caravelle, La Colombe d'Or, Lafayette, La Lunchonette, Laurent, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, Le Perigord, L'Etoile, Little Nell's Tea Room, Lola, Lutece, Maruzzella, Mayfair Regent, Metro, Mezzogiorno, Mickey Mantle's, Miracle Grill, Mondrian, Montrachet, Mortimer's, Oyster Bar & Restaurant, Popeye's Famous Fried Chicken, Positano, Positively 104th Street Cafe, Post House, Provence, Quatorze, Rainbow Promenade Bar & Rainbow Room, Rakel, River Cafe, San Domenico, Sarabeth's Kitchen, Serendipity, Sfuzzi, Shun Lee Cafe, Sign of the Dove, Sparks Steak House, Star Fish Grill, Slyvia's, Trattoria Dell'Arte, Trixies, Vico, Water Club, Windows on the World, World Yacht Cruises.) "Ask Gael: New Ideas for Places to Go in '89."
    -2/20/89. (John's, Algonquin, Mayfair Regent, Cafe Pierre, Polo, Palm Court, Stanhope, American Festival Cafe, Auntie Yuan, Chin Chin, La Metairie, Time & Again, Pete's Tavern, Sidewalkers, Barbetta, Cafe Trevi, Fortune Garden Pavilion, Carlyle, Royalton, Mayfair Regent, Le Cirque, Box Tree Hotel, Brasserie, Empire Diner). "Fine Romance."
    -3/6/89. (Rosolio). "Park Bistro." P. 58
    -3/13/89. (Duane Park, Giorgio Cafe). "Miso Italian." P. 60
    -3/27/89. (An American Place). "Larry's Home Cooking." P. 72
    -4/17/89. (Tirami su, Delia's). "Dessert Song." P. 58
  - May 15, 1989 - April 9, 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 13)
    -5/15/89. NYM, Vol.22, issue 20 (Jane's Bar & Grill, Beau Geste). "Plain and Too Fancy." P. 106
    -6/5/89. NYM Vol 22, issue 23 (Sette Mezzo, Bar du Theatre). "Kitchen Cousins." P. 97
    -6/26/89. NYM, Vol 22, issue 26 (Malvasia, Le Madri). "The Most Happy Villa." P. 51
    -7/17/89.NYM, Vol 22, issue 28 (150 Wooster). "Brian's Body Shop." P.44
    -7/24/89. NYM, Vol 22, issue 29 (El Amparo, La Trainera, El Cuchi, Casa Lucio, Lhardy, Zalacain, Museo del Jamon, Casa Labra, La Trucha, La Torre del Oro, Jose Luis, Mallorca, Bocaito, La Albariza, Kiosco de las Flores, Buenaventura, El Giralda, La Dorada, Egana Oriza, La Bobadilla, Bar Pinocho, Salo de Te Mauri, Casa Tejada, Casa Leopoldo, 7 Portes, El Salmonete, Eldorado Petit.) "Sizzling Spain." P.34
    -7/31/89. NYM, Vol 22, issue 30 (Adrienne). "Swiss Watch."p.58
    -8/14/89.NYM, Vol 22, issue 32(Alison on Dominick Street, Flamingo East). "Tripping the Bite Fantastic." P.73
    -9/18/89. NYM, Vol 22, issue 37 (Chinzan-So). "Jersey's Japanese Gem." P. 60
    -10/9/89. NYM, Vol 22, issue 40 (Vucciria, Ferrier). "Mixed Blessings." P. 70
    -10/16/89NYM, Vol 22, issue 41. (Le Cygne, Mon Cher Ton-Ton). "Swan's Way." P. 76
    -10/30/89. NYM. Vol,22, issue 43 (150 Wooster). "Hotter Than Hot: Why They Kill to Get Into 150 Wooster." P. 44
    -11/20/89. NYM, Vol 47, issue 46 (44 at the Royalton). "Royalton Flush." P. 105
    -11/27/89. NYM, Vol, 22, issue 47 "The Real Thing." (Le Bistrot de 'Etoile; La Rotisserie du Beaujolais; Au Chatelet Gourmand; L'Ami Louis;La Petite Bretonniere; La Merenda; p. 50
    -12/25/89-1/1/90. NYM, Vol 22, issue 51Downtown. (Union Square Cafe, Da Umberto, Periyali, Gotham Bar and Grill, Lola, Giorgio Cafe, Sofi, Le Madri, La Boheme, La Tulipe, John's Pizzeria, Il Mulino, Provence, 150 Wooster, Jerry's, Soho Kitchen, Alison on Dominick Street, Arqua, Montrachet, Chanterelle, Odeon, Canal Bar). "Eating to the Beat." P. 96
    -1/8/90. v. 23 # 1 (Adrienne, Alison on Dominick Street, An American Place, Arizona 206, Arizona 206 Cafe, Arqua, Arthur's Landing, Auntie Yuan, Aureole, Ballroom, Bellevues, Bistro Du Nord, Bo Ky, Cafe Edison, Cafe Iguana, Cafe Luxembourg, Cafe Spiga, Chez Louis, Chun Cha Fu, Da Umberto, David K's, Duane Park Cafe, Ecce Panis, Extra!Extra!, Ferrier, 44, Four Seasons, Gotham Bar & Grill, Houlihan's, Hudson River Club, Isand, Jane's Bar & Grill, La Caravelle, Lafayette, Le Bernardin, Le Cirque, Le Cygne, Le Madri, Living Room, Lola, Lucky Strike, Lutece, Malvasia, Michel's, Mickey Mantle, Montrachet, 150 Wooster, Orso, Out of Arcadia, Palio, Paper Moon Milano, Park Bistro, Periyali, Peter Luger Steak House, Petrossian, Pig Heaven, Poiret, Provence, Rainbow Room, Rakel, Rose Cafe, San Domenico, Sandro's, Saranac, Serendipity, Sette Mezzo, Shun Lee Cafe, Shun Lee Palace, Spark's Steak House, Smphony Cafe, Tai Hong Lau, Union Square Cafe, Vico, Yellowfingers). Ask Gael: "Eating into the Nineties." P.26
    -2/26/90. NYM, Vol 23, issue 23 (Cafe Rakel, Rose Cafe). "Ballad of the Glad Cafés." P.116
    -3/5/90. NYM, Vol 23, issue 9 (Gérard Place, Barrow Street Bistro). "Trading Places." P.58
    -3/19/90. NYM, Vol. 23. Issue 11(Lafayette). "The Drake's Progress." P.78
    -3/26/90.NYM, Vol 23, issue 12 (Pierre's, Sheba). "Playing with Fire." P.60
    -4/2/90.NYM, Vol23.. issue 13 (Nick & Eddie). "Spring Street Fever." P.89
    -4/9/90. NYM Vol 23, issue 14 (Punsch). "Punsch Line." P.86
  - April 23, 1990 - December 3, 1990 (Box 14)
    -4/23/90. (Shinwa, Thai House). "Feasts of the East."
    -4/30/90. (Lucky Strike). "Feeding Frenzy."
    -5/7/90. (J.J. Applebaum's Deli, Chinatown Express, Sbarro, Gyro II, Sushi King, Wendy's, Ballroom). "Garden Variety."
    -6/11/90. (Hudson River Café, Le Pactole, Edward Moran Bar &Grill). "Recharging Battery."
    -6/18/90. (Coyote Grill, Quatorze Bis). "Brendan Walsh Does Summer Stock."
    -6/25/90. (Laura Belle, Grolier). "Club Sandwich."
    -7/23/90. A Short Tour de France. (Maison Blanche;Restaurant Yvan; Miravile; Vivarois;; Faucher; Alain Chapel; Auberge du Grande ) p. 40
    -7/30/90. (Le Bernardin and E.A.T.) "Loaves and Fishes." P.46
    -8/13/90. (Alo Alo). "Alo Again."p. 66
    -8/20/90. NYM: Fast Track: "Bush heads for the Mountains." P. 32
    -9/17/90 NYM: Fast Track p. 22
    -9/24/90. (Arcadia, Park Bistro, Park Avenue Gourmandises). "Tried and True." P. 97
    -10/1/90. (Tatou). "Tatou Parlor." P. 52
    -10/8/90. (Prix Fixe). "The Fixe Is In." p. 57
    -10/15/90. (Le Comptoir, Café). "Paris When It Sizzles." P.64
    -10/29/90. (The Chefs Cuisiners Club). " Ay, There's The Club." P. 95
    -11/5/90.NYM. Vol 23, issue 43 "Of Cabbages And Kings" (Vince & Eddies) P.88
    -11/12/90. (Remi, Mark's). "Venice Served." P. 76
    -11/19/90. (Jour et Nuit). "Bon Jour Et Nuit." P. 74
    -12/3/90. NYM, Vol. 23, issue 47 (Les Halles, Cafe Cassis). "The French Connection. P.181
  - December 10, 1990 - October 28, 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 15)